white-wolf.com 2017-11-16

# Privacy - White Wolf Publishing

White Wolf Publishing (“White Wolf,” “we” or “us”) respect your privacy and are committed to complying fully with Swedish laws and regulations regarding online privacy protection, and any information you provide to White Wolf via [www.white-wolf.com](http://www.white-wolf.com/) (the “Site”) will be treated in accordance with those laws and regulations and as set forth herein this privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”). Visitors to the Site from outside Sweden are advised that this Privacy Policy is intended to meet the laws and requirements of Sweden, which may not be the same as the laws and regulations of your home country. 

We are providing you with this Privacy Policy in order to inform you of our policies with respect to information collected from visitors to the Site. Your use of the Site constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and your consent to the practices it describes. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SITE. 

## 1\. Automatic Collection of Anonymous Information

White Wolf may collect information including internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. We collect this information in the form of log files so that we can analyze trends, administer the Site, track users’ movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. Log files are not linked to Personally Identifiable Information (defined below). Additionally, we may use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement. 

## 2\. Personally Identifiable Information

Personally identifiable information is any information that concerns you individually and would permit someone to contact you, for example, your name, address, country of residence, telephone number, e-mail address, or any information you submit to the Site that identifies you individually (“Personally Identifiable Information”). 

We will not collect any Personally Identifiable Information about you unless you provide it. Therefore, if you do not want White Wolf to obtain any Personally Identifiable Information about you, do not submit it. 

You can visit and browse the Site without revealing Personally Identifiable Information about yourself. You may also choose to disclose Personally Identifiable Information about yourself, in order for example to receive our newsletters, which may be maintained as described below. We may collect Personally Identifiable Information about you through registration forms, which may require you to provide, without limitation, your e-mail address. Such forms may be required to receive newsletters, or to request information about White Wolf. 

Should you choose to communicate with White Wolf through e-mail, via the Site, by telephone, in writing, or through other means, we may collect the information in these communications, and such information may be Personally Identifiable Information. 

If you would like to correct or delete any Personally Identifiable Information, please take contact us.

## 3\. Information Use and Storage Period

White Wolf may use Personally Identifiable Information collected through the Site to, among other things, respond to inquiries or comments, to maintain the security and integrity of the Site and its data, to provide users with product or service updates, promotional notices, and to offer services and products of interest to users. 

White Wolf uses the anonymous information collected automatically by our servers primarily to help us administer and improve our Site. We may also use aggregated anonymous information to provide information about our Site to advertisers, potential business partners and other unaffiliated entities. Again, this information is not personally identifiable. 

White Wolf will not store Personally Identifiable Information longer than necessary for the purpose of the collection. Due to tax regulations however, White Wolf usually stores any collected information (Personally Identifiable Information and anonymous information) for a period of five (5) years. 

## 4\. Disclosure of Information

We may use unaffiliated companies to help us maintain and operate the Site or for other reasons related to the operation of our business, and those companies may receive your Personally Identifiable Information for that purpose only. We may also disclose Personally Identifiable Information about you in connection with legal requirements, such as in response to an authorized subpoena, governmental request or investigation, or as otherwise permitted by law. Finally, we may sell or buy corporate assets, and in such transactions user information may be one of the transferred business assets. If White Wolf or certain of its assets are acquired, user information may be transferred. White Wolf does not sell Personally Identifiable Information to third parties. 

## 5\. Security

White Wolf maintains physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to help guard Personally Identifiable Information. White Wolf restricts authorized access to your personal information to those persons who have a legitimate purpose to know that information to provide services to you and those persons you have authorized to have access to such information. White Wolf also has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control (e.g., verification of Site user’s identity through username and password). Please be aware, however, that any e-mail or other transmission you send through the Internet cannot be completely protected against unauthorized interception, and it is your sole responsibility to protect the secrecy of your password. 

## 6\. Children's Privacy

You must be at least 13 years of age to visit and use the Site and get our newsletter. White Wolf does not knowingly collect information from children under 13. If you are a parent or guardian of a child under 13 whom you believe has applied to get our newsletter without your authorization, please contact us. 

## 7\. External Links

This Privacy Policy does not extend to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third party vendors and other third parties to which we may link (“External Sites”). Please be aware that White Wolf is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of External Sites. External Sites may use cookies. White Wolf encourages you to read the privacy policies provided by External Sites before you provide Personally Identifiable Information to them. 

## 8\. Severance

If any of this Privacy Policy is determined to be illegal, invalid or otherwise unenforceable by reason of the laws of any state or country in which this Privacy Policy is intended to be effective, then to the extent and within the jurisdiction in which that term is illegal, invalid or unenforceable, it shall be severed and deleted from this Privacy Policy and the remaining terms of the Privacy Policy shall survive, remain in full force and effect, and continue to be binding and enforceable. 

## 9\. Governing Law/Jurisdiction

This Privacy Policy is governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of Sweden. You agree to submit to the personal jurisdiction of the courts of Stockholm, Sweden for any cause of action arising out of or relating to this Privacy Policy, and hereby waive any right to participate in any type of law suit brought and/or maintained as a class action or similar in nature to a class action, to the extent permissible by applicable law. 

## 10\. Modifications of this Privacy Policy

White Wolf shall have the right, at its sole discretion, to modify, add or remove any terms or conditions of this Privacy Policy without notice or liability to you. Any changes to the Privacy Policy shall be effective immediately following the posting of any such changes on the Site. Please review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure you are aware of any changes made by White Wolf. Your continued use of the Site after changes are posted means you agree to be legally bound by this Privacy Policy as updated and amended, to the extent permissible by applicable law. 

White Wolf AB

Date last modified: October 5, 2015
